Find your place among the stars.
Hollywood Stargirl is a comedy, romance, music film directed by Julia Hart.
When Stargirl's mother is hired as the costume designer on a movie, they relocate to L.A.,
where Stargirl quickly becomes involved with an eclectic assortment of characters.
Susan "Stargirl" Caraway, played by Grace VanderWaal.
Ana Caraway, played by Judy Greer.
Evan, played by Elijah Richardson.
Roxanne Martel, played by Uma Thurman.
Terrell, played by Tyrel Jackson Williams.
Mr. Mitchell, played by Judd Hirsch.
Hollywood Stargirl is a 2022 American teen romantic drama film directed by Julia
Hart from a screenplay that she co-wrote with Jordan Horowitz.
The film is a sequel to the 2020 film Stargirl, which was in turn based on Jerry Spinelli's 2000
novel of the same name; it is not an adaptation of the novel's sequel Love, Stargirl.
The story follows Stargirl and her mother Ana, who is hired as the costume designer on a movie, as they relocate to Los
Angeles, where Stargirl meets new friends and explores her creative side, gaining success as a performer.
The film premiered on May 23, 2022, at the El Capitan Theatre in Los
Angeles, California, and was released on Disney+ on June 3, 2022.
It received positive reviews.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.